hotmaths.com.au 2015-05-10

# Privacy

### What is this policy about?

  * This policy covers the gathering and handling of personally identifiable information by HOTmaths Pty Ltd (HOTmaths), when you register to use our online mathematics program, Cambridge HOTmaths. 
  * This policy does not cover the practices of people, organisations or companies for which HOTmaths does not have responsibility. 

### What information does HOTmaths collect and why?

HOTmaths collects information that identifies you when you use Cambridge HOTmaths. This includes your first and last name, a username, a password, your email address, subscriber type, school and postcode.

Designated Cambridge HOTmaths school administrators can also access this data to help them manage school subscriptions. They are required to treat this information as confidential.

  * Your username and password is required so that only you can access your account. 
  * For students and teachers using Cambridge HOTmaths as part of a school program, your first and last name is required to allow us to place your subscription into a learning management system. For students and teachers using Cambridge HOTmaths as an individual, with no affiliation with a school, you may use a pseudonym. 
  * Your email address is required so that HOTmaths can contact you about changes to the site or advise you of matters regarding your use of the site. 
  * Your email address may also be used occasionally to send you product information. If you do not wish to receive this information, please email us at contactus@hotmaths.com.au or telephone us on 1300 887 907 to advise us. 
  * Your subscription type tells HOTmaths whether you are a student or a teacher, and is required so that we can create the appropriate subscription for you. 
  * Name of school is required for students and teachers using Cambridge HOTmaths as part of a school-based program. It is required to allow us to place your subscription into a learning management system. 
  * Your postcode is required to assist HOTmaths in analyzing student demand geographically.

### Collection of information from social media

  * HOTmaths may collect personally identifiable information from social media. This will only be done if you contact us through one of our social media channels, and the collection of this information is in accordance with the terms of use of the social media channel. 
  * Information collected from social media is covered by this privacy policy.

### Use of cookies

  * HOTmaths uses cookies with Cambridge HOTmaths.
  * Cookies are small amounts of information that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your web browser. They tell us when you have visited our site and where you have been. They do not identify you personally, just the presence of your browser. 
  * Cookies make it easier for you to log on and use the site during future visits. They also ensure that only one person can access your account at any time. 
  * Should you wish to do so, your browser's help section should be able to warn you before accepting cookies and how to filter or disable them, although if you do filter or disable cookies, you may not be able to use certain features on Cambridge HOTmaths. 
  * HOTmaths does not collect any information such as date and time of visit by anyone visiting the public sections of the site without logging in to a Cambridge HOTmaths subscription. 

### Information storage, sharing and disclosure

  * HOTmaths and our affiliate Cambridge University Press will both have access to your information.
  * Your information is held in private databases only accessible to HOTmaths and Cambridge University Press employees in Australia. Our private databases are on servers located in the United States, and we have taken steps to ensure that our service providers handle your information in a manner broadly consistent with Australian privacy law. 
  * Your information is also held in commercial customer relationship management databases (CRMs). These CRMs may store your data overseas, but the data can only be accessed by HOTmaths and Cambridge University Press employees. 
  * We may occasionally provide your information to third party distributors within Australia for the purpose of managing your school subscription. The information we will provide is your first and last name, school, school address, username and password. 
  * If you have nominated an overseas country as your location or the location of your educational institution, we may occasionally provide your information to Cambridge University Press staff and/or third party distributors in this country or region for the purpose of managing your school subscription. The information we will provide is your first and last name, school, school address, username and password. 
  * Please email us if you do not wish for your data to be shared with Cambridge University Press employees outside Australia or third party distributors. 

### Exceptions

  * The only exception to the our information storage, sharing and disclosure terms would be if HOTmaths or Cambridge University Press were required by a court order or subpoena or relevant laws to provide information including where relevant to legal misuse of the site or for enforcement related activity. 

### Your control over your personally identifying information

  * You are entitled to see the information held about you and you may ask us to make any necessary changes to ensure that it is accurate and up to date. If you wish to do this, please email us at contactus@hotmaths.com.au. 
  * Some personally identifying information collected by HOTmaths can be edited and changed by you through the 'Account settings' section inside the Cambridge HOTmaths site. 
  * No person other than you, HOTmaths staff and Cambridge University Press staff, and designated Cambridge HOTmaths administrators at your school can access these details. HOTmaths and Cambridge University Press would only manually edit your details if a designated Cambridge HOTmaths administrator at your school requested that this be done. 

### Security of information

  * Your personal information is password protected. For your own protection, do not allow anyone else to know or use your password. 
  * SSL encryption is used in some areas of the site where sensitive data is transmitted.

### Changes to this policy

HOTmaths may change this policy from time to time. If it does so, you will be notified by a message in your Cambridge HOTmaths message centre.

### Complaints

If you would like to lodge a complaint about our privacy policies or the storage and treatment of your personal information, please email us at contactus@hotmaths.com.au marked for the attention of the HOTmaths Privacy Officer. We will review your complaint and respond to you within 5 business days.

### Further information

If you would like further information about this policy, or would like to request a printed version of this policy, please email us at contactus@hotmaths.com.au or call us on 1300 887 907.
